SAM MILLAR

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Self-determined Computer Science major currently attending Arizona State University, with 3+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of customer communications, customer satisfaction, and contract compliance skills to successfully fill the role at your company. Frequently praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Arizona State University's Fulton School of Engineering

Computer Science Tutor, Tempe, AZ / Januarry 2020 - Present

- Tutoring Freshman, Sophomores, and Juniors the core concepts of the ASU Computer Science curriculum
- Virtual Tutoring for ASU Online Computer Science Students
- Provided academic support for struggling students

Elevate Tickets

Client Services Intern, Tempe, AZ / February 2019 – December 2019

- Shadowed Software Engineering and QA teams develop software including websites and ticketing purchase software
- Traveled to Music Festivals to perform Onsite IT
- Customer Service Representative

Arizona State University Aquatics

Lifeguard and Maintenance Technician, Tempe, AZ / May 2018 – Jan 2020

- Lifeguard at Sun Devil Fitness Complex
- Lifeguard at Mona Plummer Aquatic Complex, Home of ASU Division 1 Aquatics Program
- Maintenance Technician at Mona Plummer Aquatic Complex

sammillarrr@gmail.com

- (562) 243 8943
- Tempe, AZ

EDUCATION

ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY

Tempe, AZ

B.S. Computer Science Candidate (Expected graduation May 2020) Awards & Honors

> New American University Scholarship (Dean's List)

Extracurricular Activities

- ASU Mobile Devs
- ASU Poker Club
- Software Developers Association (SoDA)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Public Speaking Works Well Under Pressure Adaptable Quick Learner Strong Computer Skills

REFERENCES

References available upon request